# ELLIZEU RODRIGUES SENA

Electronic and Computer Engineer

#### About Me

Developer passionate about new challenges, I have worked on technology projects in two continents (Europe and America). Strong knowledge of agile methodologies and I work well in teams. Entrepreneurial spirit!

- **\*** 11/21/1999
- **)** +55 (21) 97261-6385
- ✓ ellizeurs@hotmail.com
- () /ellizeurs
- in /ellizeurs
- Rio de Janeiro

# Skills

- C++, C, Python, Bash, PHP,
  Javascript, JQuery, React, Node, C#,
  Java, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MatLab
- A {MS, Libre, GSuite} Office
- tinux, Windows
- VsCode
- 🚣 Scrum, DevOps

#### Languages

- A Portuguese (C2)
- English (C1)

$\overline{}$				
()	Q-	$\cap$	Г۱۱	/F

My goal is to work in the fields of electronics and computer engineering, focusing on computing, data science, web development, and machine learning.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **FundX Academy**

Backend Developer | Tech Leader, Full-Time
MAY 2022 - OCT 2022

#### **Energy Research Company**

Data Scientist, Part-Time

OCT 2021 - OCT 2023

#### Universinagem

Backend Developer, Full-Time

OCT 2019 -

#### **Minerva Rockets**

Innovation Engineer, Part-Time

OCT 2019 - MAR 2022

#### **EDUCATION**

# Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (Master's)

RIO DE JANEIRO, RJ 2024 - Electrical Engineering

# Federal University of Rio de Janeiro (Bachelor's)

RIO DE JANEIRO, RJ 2017 - 2024

**Electronic and Computer Engineering** 

Thesis topic: Time Series Prediction of Biodiesel Prices using Neural Networks

# FAETEC RJ - E.T.E. João Luiz do Nascimento (High School and Technical)

Nova Iguaçu, RJ 2014 - 2016 Technical in Electronics